啥事
What's up?
景色不错
Great view.
我是说海港
Harbor, I mean.
真它妈的风景如画 没错
It's fucking picturesque, is what it is.
每天早晨我都问自己 我今天是不是该
Every morning I ask myself, "Is today the day I drive down...
去Fort Armistead 望着海港发呆
"to Fort Armistead, stare out at the harbor?"
我最终决定不去 因为就算我安守本分
No, I figure eventually, if I mind my own business...
Frank叔叔也会在早晨七点叫醒我
Uncle Frank will wake my ass up at 7:00 in the morning...
神秘兮兮地叫我过来 于是乎我来了
tell me to get my ass down there for some mysterious fucking reason.
有不错的停泊口 不错的起重机...
Good anchorage, good cranes...
不错的铁路 离I95州际公路又近 还有很多待命的劳动力 不是吗?
good railroads, close to l-95. Lot of people ready to work, right?
这就是我的小镇!
That's my fucking town.
只是 我们距离Hampton锚地有110英里...
Except, the thing is, we're another 1 10 miles...
那里的船要到这里就会多出一天的行程
for any ship coming up from Hampton Roads. An extra day.
那干嘛还要来这儿?
So why come?
除非你知道货物能又快又好地
Unless you know your cargo's gonna move fast...
在港口处理掉 否则为什么要来呢?
and clean through the port.
干嘛要来Baltimore卸货呢? 除非那里的家伙
Why offload in Baltimore, except that a Baltimore gang...
能让你的船比在其他港口更快返航...
can turn your ship around faster than any other port...
能确保你的货物...
and will make sure your cargo...
你所有的货物 去该去的地方 比任何码头都流动得快
all your cargo, gets where it needs to go faster than anywhere else.
说得你们从前从没偷过东西似的
Like you guys never stole nothing back in the day.
现在不是从前了 Nicky
We ain't back in the day, Nicky.
你上次见到卡车在Patapsco中转站外
When was the last time you saw trucks backed up
排成三英里的长队是什么时候?
for three miles outside Patapsco terminal?
要不是有运车船(大型滚轮船) 我们早就饿肚子了
If it wasn't for the car-ships, we would be starving.
把照相机还回来
The cameras come back.
说真的 今天就送回来
I'm serious. They come back today,
我们告诉承运商 集装箱落在了堆货区
we tell the shipper we lost the can in the stacks.
没了
They're gone.
我们已经转手了
We turned them over already.
给谁了?
To who?
TASCO:跨大西洋集装箱服务公司
你瞧 TASCO就要把生意转移到Norfolk港去了
You know the Tasco line's a cunt hair away from taking their business down to Norfolk.
- 眼下我不要麻烦事 - 可我需要 Frank叔叔 我需要钱
- I don't need this shit right now. - I do, Uncle Frank, I need the money.
它妈的 你根本不在听!
You ain't hearing me!
你以为我过得容易吗?
What? You think this shit is easy?
你认为它妈的很容易吗?
You think it's fucking easy?
你试试看一个月工作五六天
You try living on five or six days a month.
看你多快变成穷光蛋
See how fast it puts you on your ass.
我穷得叮当响了 Frank叔叔
I am on my ass, Uncle Frank.
你要钱 来找我
You need money, you come to me.
Frankie Sobotka最近是码头上 它妈的圣诞老人
Frankie Sobotka is Father fucking Christmas on the docks lately.
- 难怪 他口袋满着呢 - 你以为这都是为我自己吗?
- No doubt, his pockets are full. - You think it's for me?
你这么想吗?
Is that what you think?
才不是为了我自己 Nick!
It ain't about me, Nick!
我知道 对不起
I know, I'm sorry.
你让Ziggy也搅和进来了 天啊 Nick 你它妈的在想什么呢?
You got Ziggy mixed up in this. Jesus, Nick, what the fuck are you thinking?
我和Zig要好好谈这件事
Me and Zig are gonna talk on this long and hard.
走吧 我们干活去
Come on, let's go to work.
多少?
How much?
2万
Twenty.
三人分
Three-way split.
谁是内线?
Who's the inside man?
你不知道?
You don't know?
去你的 我不打小报告
Fuck you then, I ain't no snitch.
谁都别太招摇了 你懂吧?
Nobody should flash too much money. You know that much, right?
嗯
Yeah.
火线重案组 第二季 第四集 困难重重
The Wire S02E04 Hard Cases
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"听到音乐 我就要起舞"  ---Greggs
毒性强 有兴奋作用 常作老鼠药
毒物分析报告里番木鳖碱成阳性
Toxicology's coming back positive for strychnine.
10% 12% 添加得很巧妙
10%, 12%. It's pretty well laced.
是蓄意吗?
This was intentional?
那得验尸官说了算 不过我已经见惯了在这种街头零售的毒品里
That's the ME's call, but I've seen street packages cut all the time...
添加各种化学剂
with all kinds of chemicals.
真的  不用加太多 就能让很稀的货变得很给力
You don't use too much, you give a weak package some kick.
大家以为你这货很高档 其实你给的
People start thinking you're high-grade, when what you got is...
不过是混着老鼠药的垃圾货
stepped-on trash with a little bit of rat poison mixed in.
可是老鼠药掺太多了就会死人 就像现在这情况
Too much rat poison, you got people falling out, like we got.
妥善回答那些记者的提问
Be nice to have a few answers for those reporters.
他们想知道什么?
What do they wanna know?
事情是如何发生的 我们在干嘛 老一套
How it got in, what we're doing, the usual.
这玩意儿跟所有东西一样 都是混进来的
It got in like everything gets in.
如果在监狱里 我们都战胜不了毒品
If you can't win the war on drugs in a prison...
那还能在哪里取胜呢? 我倒是要问问你
where the hell you gonna win it? I ask you.
听着 如果只死了一两个人 事情会过去
Listen, if it were one or two dead, it would fade.
可是一夜死了五个人 医务室里还躺着八个?
But five in one night, and eight more in the infirmary?
我们得表态了
We need to show the flag on this.
我需要你们给我一点促谈的价码
What I'm gonna need is for you all to wheel and deal.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
如果要靠线人告密才能查下去
If this case gets made from an informant...
那么提供一些减刑的条件...
and you're gonna have a couple dozen of them...
你就能找到不少这样的人
if you're ready to shave some years.
警监
Colonel.
- Jimmy - Winona
- Jimmy. - Winona.
出自情景喜剧"Gilligan的小岛" 主角是名船员 绰号"小家伙"
Gilligan 小家伙
Gilligan, little buddy.
你没有工作吗?
Don't you have a job?
我闻到新鲜的查案味道
I smell fresh police work.
好吧 保持下去
Okay, be like that.
你从集装箱里有找到了一些文件?
You got some paper from inside the can?
一封信 几个信封和一些碎纸片?
A letter, couple of envelopes, some scraps of stuff?
是的 所有东西都交个物证处了
Yeah, everything's down in your evidence control.
你有提交单吗?
You got the submission slips?
他有
He does.
Lester
Lester.
你都要拿出来吗?
You want to pull all of it?
慢着
Hold it.
在你和你的无名氏开始"共舞"前...
Before you start dancing with your Jane Doe...
我需要你在Gant案上帮我一下
I'm gonna need a little something from you on the Gant case.
我的私处还有llene Nathan的一排牙印呢
I got a full set of llene Nathan's teeth marks on my hind parts.
- 没问题 我罩着你 - 你找到Omar了?
- No problem, I got you covered. - You found Omar?
我从没弄丢过他 伙计
I never lost him, my friend.
他找到Omar了?
He's got Omar?
胡说
Bullshit.
Omar是谁?
Who's Omar?
我的辞呈已经交上来了
My papers are in.
没错
They are.
没错 你想走就走吧
You want out, you're out.
不过我在此提议
But I'm offering to clean the slate here.
咱俩能不计前嫌
You and me.
为什么?
Why?
下周委员会将投票选举 之后我就升迁了
The council vote is next week, after which I'm upstairs.
如果我要在这里做出一些功绩
Now, if I'm gonna give myself a chance to make my mark on this place,
我就需要优秀的人才
I'll need good people.
你可以信任的人才
People you can trust.
你不是吗?
And you ain't that?
是的 你是有心机
All right. You're a snake.
但你也熟谙自己的业务
But you seem to know your business.
一个月后我就要参加律师资格考试了
I'm taking the bar exam in a month.
何不推迟一两年...
Why not put it off for a year or two...
带着警监的抚恤金再走?
Ieave the department with a major's pension?
Scalise将在今年夏天退休
Scalise is gonna retire this summer.
带好东南区这个专案组
You do me a good turn on this detail in southeast...
这个职位就归你了
and you'll have that posting.
你为什么这么做?
Why would you do that?
我器重你 Cedric
I value you, Cedric.
你的确自负又不忠
You're arrogant and disloyal.
不过或许给你点时间 你能让自己绽放光芒
But maybe, given time, you'll find a way to shine.
什么小组?
What's the detail?
大概是毒品案
Drug case, probably.
我感觉是Stan Valchek
My sense of it is that Stan Valchek has got...
和港口工会里的谁结下了私怨
some personal issues with somebody in one of the port unions.
他觉得他们太阔绰了
He thinks they've got too much money.
于是 Valchek如他所愿成立了专案组
And so, being Valchek, he gets a detail.
就这样? 有点空穴来风
That it? Pretty thin.
我不在乎你是否真给Valchek办出个案子
I don't care if you make a case for Valchek or not.
我只在乎那个波兰老家伙解散小组的时候
I do care that the old Polack comes away from it...
觉得他花的钱值了
feeling he got his money's worth.
Valchek点名要我 对吧?
Valchek asked for me by name, didn't he?
你们俩做交易 需要我来当筹码
You two are trading horses and you need me in the corral.
这样吧
How about this?
如果我拿下这案子
If I bring in the case...
你就让这个专案组永久作为
you make the detail permanent as a major case unit...
刑侦部的一个单位
within CID.
行
Fair enough.
只要能安抚好Valchek 破一两桩毒品案子
Just keep Valchek stroked and make sure you bring in a drug case or two.
还有一个条件
One other thing.
升迁和承诺建组还不够?
A promotion and the promise of a specialized unit isn't enough?
人要我自己挑
I choose my own people.
折腾我一次 是你可耻
Fuck me once, shame on you.
- 折腾我第二次... - 开名单吧
- Fuck me twice-- - Make a list.
拿给Rawls 你要谁他会帮你调配
Give it to Rawls. He'll pull who you want.
它妈的说不通啊 其中有些人无足轻重啊
The shit do not make sense. Some of them wasn't about nothing.
我是说 Tae? Lizard? 如果真是毒里下毒
I mean, Tae? Lizard? lf it was a hotshot...
那么他们目标都是群小喽啰呢
they were after some real lightweight motherfucks.
嘿 Dee 你要看银影侠吗?(漫画神奇四侠中角色)
Yo, Dee, you want any Silver Surfers?
他们把Tae房里的东西都扔出来了
They tossing shit Tae had in his cell, man.
不管是谁掺的货  肯定不知道自己在干啥
Whoever load that shit up didn't know what he was doing.
我在医务室的哥们说 那货与其说是毒品 还不如说是老鼠药
My boy down the infirmary say the shit was more rat poison than it was dope.
它妈的这就对了
Fucking-A right.
无名氏 5号
Jane Doe, number five.
5号
Five.
你好啊 宝贝?
What's up, baby?
别在这里 收起来
Not here, put it away.
威士忌加啤(蓝领常爱喝的一种调酒) 亲爱的
Shot and a beer, darling.
给你自己留了一个哈?
Kept one for yourself, did you?
那些日本佬 照相机倒是做的不错 嗯
Them Japs, they make a nice little camera, they do.
- 那玩意儿里有胶卷吗? - 不 这是数码的
-You even got film in that bitch? -No, it's digital.
我知道是数码的 那又怎样?
I know it's digital, so what?
所以没有胶卷 看 里面有芯片
So, no film, look, there's a computer chip inside.
把它拿出来 就可以把照片上传到电脑上
You take that off, you load the pictures onto the computer.
多谢
Thanks.
Zig
Zig.
Ziggy
Ziggy.
暂时别到处撒钱 好吗?
Don't spread no cash around for a while, all right?
我当然不会啦
Hell, no.
我可能就给"公主"(Zig的爱车)换个新离合器片罢了
I might get a new clutch plate put in Princess is all.
还有 你爸知道了
Also, your father knows.
他怎么会知道?
How does he know?
"马面"看见我们了 不是吗?
Horse saw us, right?
我操 他说了?
Fuck me, he told?
"马面"和你老爸那么铁 他当然说了
How long has Horse been tight with your pop? Of course he told.
他很生气 Zig 很不高兴
He's pissed, Zig. He ain't happy.
你怎么说的?
What did you say?
我告诉他 我们已经把相机脱手了...
I told him we already turned the cameras around...
过了一会儿 他就不骂了
and after a while, he stopped yelling.
可能不骂你了
At you, maybe.
无论如何
Anyway.
暂时低调点 行吗?
It's low profile for a while, all right?
好吧
All right.
那你用这个照相 就不用去照相馆...
You take a picture on that, you don't have to take it to photomart...
- 洗照片吗? - 不用 直接上传电脑
- to get it turned around? - No, it goes on a computer.
我去撒泡尿
I got to take a leak.
下一个我 好吗?
I go next, all right?
漂亮男孩 嘿 哈
Pretty boy. Hey, there.
天啊 Zig
Christ, Ziggy.
Jimmy 和你说一下安排
Jimmy, just a scheduling thing.
周六Sean被邀请 去Mark Lohrman的生日派对
Sean was invited to Mark Lohrman's birthday party on Saturday.
2点后你可以去那里接他
So you can pick him up there after 2:00.
我知道这是你的周末 可如果Sean错过了他会难过的
I realize it's your weekend, but Sean would be upset if he missed it.
行吗? 好极了
Okay? Great.
周末前找到Omar Jimmy Ilene很恼火
Omar by the end of the week, Jimmy. Ilene is on the warpath.
操蛋的 我是认真的
Motherfucker, I am serious.
McNulty先生 Halpern医生的办公室来电
Mr. McNulty, this is Dr. Halpern's office.
周二你错过了六个月一次的洗牙
You missed your six-month cleaning on Tuesday...
我们也很久没有和你联系了
and we haven't heard from you.
请给我们回个电话
Give us a call, please.
McNulty 我是你亲爱的朋友llene Nathan
McNulty, this is your dear friend llene Nathan.
我会上诉这宗破案
I indicted this piece-of-shit case...
全仗你发誓 我们有目击证人...
because you swore to me we had an eyeball witness....
现在是早晨6点38分 上班开车时间 据报道....
Drive time is 6:38 in the a.m. and we have reports of a....
滚开 混蛋
Go around, asshole.
你叫我啥?
What'd you call me?
我睡在这边呢
I'm sleeping on this side.
就因为你要起床 所有人都得起吗?
Because you got to get up, everybody does?
没错
Yup.
把坐便器擦干净 Nick 我知道你尿上去了
Wipe off the seat, Nick, I know you hit it.
要是我现在可以放屁 我就放了
If I could fart now, I would.
真是出人意料啊
That's a surprise.
没时间吃早饭吗?
No chance for breakfast?
不 我顺路去酒吧吃早饭
No. I'll stop by the bar.
不行 你没这么多时间
No, you won't. You ain't got time.
你得送我去我妈家接Ashley
You got to run me past my ma's to pick up Ashley.
妈的 那就赶快 你知道今天我有一艘船要卸呢
Shit, hurry up, then. You know I got a ship to work today.
你妈也知道你有一艘船
Your ma knows you got a ship, too.
别上楼了 直接从后门出去
Don't go upstairs. Just head out the back.
我在巷子后面接你 行吗?
I'll pick you up at the back of the alley, all right?
天啊 Nicky 我们都有孩子了
Jesus, Nicky, we got a kid together.
我们在你家人的地下室过一夜 有什么大不了?
What's the big deal we spend the night in your folks' basement?
他们是体面人
They're decent people.
- 我们没时间了 - 我知道
- We ain't got time. - I know.
那你还抓什么?
So, why you grabbing?
它们盯着我看呢
They were staring right at me.
屋后见
I'll meet you out back.
那么集装箱是如何卸船离港的?
So how do you get the container off the ship, off the dock?
我觉得如果你不想你的货被乱放
I guess if you wanted to make sure your cargo isn't messed with,
你得要联系好一名检验员
you'd want to get with one of the checkers.
- 他们是谁? - 当地15和14分局
- Who are they? - Local 1514.
他们监视所有的装货和卸货
They monitor all the loading and offloading...
他们核对货物清单 清点货物
they match the manifests, they tally the cargo.
所有进出的货物 都需要通过他们才能安放在某处
Nothing goes in or out without them putting it down somewhere.
- 或不放 - 或不放
- Or not. - Or not.
那我们要找个检验员谈谈
So we need to talk to a checker.
咋了?
What?
黑人 白人 波兰人 爱尔兰人 意大利人 不论什么人
Black, white, Polish, lrish, ltalian, it doesn't matter.
谁都不会向警察开口
No one talks to police.
那你怎么立案呢?
How do you make a case then?
我巡逻
I patrol.
我写交通罚单
I write traffic tickets.
如果我们发现开封的集装箱 或者被损坏的集装箱...
If we got an open container, or a damaged container...
我写份报告
I take a report.
有东西丢了 再写份报告
We got something stolen, I take another report.
有人被砸了 或者被前端装载机压过去
Someone gets something dropped on him or gets run over by a front-end loader...
- 我接着写报告 - 这就是工作咯
- I keep writing. - That's the job?
你干了多久?
How long you been on?
2年
Two years.
之前你是做什么的?
What did you do before that?
我在Fort McHenry隧道收通行费
I took tolls from people at the Fort McHenry tunnel.
我很高兴地说 那份工作没有这份来得有趣
Which, I'm happy to say, wasn't nearly as much fun.
一年22500美元 每晚到家都精疲力竭...
Made $22,500 and went home tired every night...
直到一天晚上 我走过办公室公告牌
until I walked by the office bulletin board one night...
读了密歇根交通部的岗位招聘
read the MDOT job posting.
港口警务员 日班  起薪33000美元 外加福利
Port Authority officers, Schedule one, starting at $33,000 with benefits.
就不去收通行费了?
Toll-taking days were over?
我两个孩子的父亲99年去了休斯敦
Father of my two kids went to Houston in '99...
三年来没怎么联系
hasn't so much as called in three years.
就靠22500美元过得艰难啊
I wasn't gonna make it on $22,500.
特别是还带着孩子 难啊
Not with kids, I wasn't.
你真想当警察?
Did you want to be a police?
那天晚上死的可能是我
Could've been me the other night.
没错
True.
只是突然间 你冒了出来 阻止我
Except for all of a sudden, you up and tell me to stop doing that.
Avon来相救了 你怎么知道的?
Avon to the rescue. How did you know?
我以为你来这里
I figured you were gonna be bringing your ass in here...
是感谢我阻止了你
to thank me for pulling you off of that shit.
死了五个人
Five dead.
医务室里还躺着更多
More in the infirmary.
你是怎么知道的?
How did you know?
我只是做个舅舅该做的
I did as your uncle should...
因为我不想你毁了自己
because I'm concerned about you fucking yourself up.
你早就知道了
You knew.
听着 兄弟 这事与我无关
Look, man, I ain't had nothing to do with it.
但是或许我知道是谁干的
I might know who did, though.
事实上你在这里呼风唤雨 还能会是谁?
You practically running this place. Who else could it be?
发生了什么不重要 懂吗?
It ain't about what happened, you understand?
重要的是好好利用这一切
It's about using what happened to our advantage.
要么玩 要么被玩
Play or you gonna get played.
我想知道不是你干的
I need to know that you ain't do that shit.
我想知道这个
That's what I need to know.
我已经说过了 你不相信就算了
I already said it. You ain't gonna believe it, fuck it.
你可以认为我主使了这事 但你该感激自己现在还能站在这里
You can tell yourself that I spiked it, but be grateful that you still standing.
感激完之后...
Once you done with all that...
我们可以讨论我们怎样减刑
we can talk about how we start shaving some of these years off.
不仅仅是给我 还有你
And not just for me, for you, too.
他们在找把货带进来的混蛋
They looking for the motherfucker who brought that shit in here.
他们要他完蛋 你猜咋的
They need him to fall. And you know what?
我可以说一个名字 一个不会错的名字
I can give you a name. I can give you the right name.
我们可以把名字告诉狱长助理...
We can take that name down to the assistant warden...
然后我们就可以少呆几年
and we can get some of our lives back.
懂吗?
You dig?
所以 跟紧我
So, stay close.
这事里应外合...
This play on the inside, this play on the outside...
我们都能搞定
we got it all covered.
你的事我不想插手了
I don't want no part of what you do no more.
听到了吗?
You hear me?
别把我扯进去就行
So you can just leave me the fuck out of that.
不管什么事
Whatever it is.
有人见过Omar吗?
Anyone seen Omar?
继续开工!
We're back in!
一天六艘船
Six ships in one day.
几个月都没看到中转站这么繁忙了 感觉真棒
Ain't seen the terminal this busy in months. Feels sweet.
妈的 瞧这小妖精
Shit, look at this pretty bitch.
你它妈的穿的什么?
What the fuck are you wearing?
意大利皮衣 懂吗?
Italian leather, all right?
大冬天 还在该死的码头上?
In the middle of winter? On the goddamn docks?
- 这玩意儿多少钱啊? - 2000美元
- How much does that shit cost? - $2,000.
就一件上衣? 你它妈的疯了吗 Zig?
For a goddamn jacket? Are you out your fucking mind, Zig?
去他的
Fuck it.
一件上衣2000美元
$2,000 for a single goddamn jacket.
天啊 Zig 你需要心理治疗
Jesus, Zig, you need therapy and shit.
我以为像你这样的美国黑人会懂..
I figured an African-American such as yourself would understand...
像我这样的花花公子为什么需要紧跟潮流
how a player such as myself needs to take heed in the latest fashion.
可是很明显 你它妈的也没品味
But apparently, you ain't got no fucking style neither.
- 我还是走路吧 好吗? - 回见
- I'm gonna walk, all right? - See you.
咋了?
What?
我是怎么跟你说不要大把花钱的?
What did I tell you about not spreading no cash around?
老天啊 Nicky 不就是它妈的外衣吗
Jesus Christ, Nicky, it's a fucking coat.
我可以和别人说我分期付款之类的
I can tell people I'm paying for it on installments or whatever.
可是你得承认 我今天看上去很帅
But you got to admit, I do look pretty today.
真的
I do.
希腊人要和我们谈谈
The Greeks wanna talk to us.
谈什么?
What about?
他们觉得我们做得很好
We did good by them.
是吗?
Yeah?
可是 看在老天的份上 Zig
But, for Christ sakes, Zig, keep your shit quiet...
在大伙都议论我们之前 别显摆了
before half the fucking waterfront's talking about us.
好的 没问题
All right, no problem.
- 嗯 回头见 - 再见
- All right. See you later. - See you.
嘿 扔了
Yo, quit it.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我们现在不必这样
We don't need that now.
- 你说啥? - 我才不在乎毒品
- Say what? - I don't give a shit about drugs.
不过乱扔垃圾让我不爽 你可以在我走了之后捡起来
Littering pisses me off, though. You can pick that up when I'm gone.
我在找一个抢劫犯 叫Omar
I'm looking for a stick-up boy, name of Omar.
黑皮肤 很瘦 脸上有道疤
Dark-skinned, thin guy with a scar right down his face.
如果你们见到他一定会认出他...
You boys would definitely know him if you saw him...
因为他有这么长的一把猎枪
because he's got a shotgun about yea-long.
他会不假思索地把枪指着你的头 抢走你的东西
He'll put it to your head and steal your shit without thinking twice.
有人知道他在哪里出没吗?
Does anyone know where he hangs?
和谁在一起?
Who he's running with?
他开什么车?
What he's driving?
去你的 警官
Fuck you, Officer.
第二包比前一包还差
The second package came even weaker than the last.
不能像以前那么分拆了
It won't take the cut like it did before.
它妈的亚特兰大的货又贵又差
Fucking Atlanta shit cost more and still not as good.
拿到的纯度才25%
Came in at 25.
我们只能把它们分一分 直接装包
All we can do is sprinkle it and bag it.
然后我亏本?
And lose my money?
我亏本了啊
I lose my money.
再稀释
Step on that motherfucker.
多少?
How hard?
10%
Make it 10.
- 已经很差了 - 我知道
- It's shit now. - I know.
集装箱这条线索已经断了 双方地址都是假的
So the container itself leads us nowhere. Fake addresses on either end.
因此我们只能从港口入手
Which leaves us the port itself.
因为不论船有什么问题
Because whatever went wrong on that ship was known to whoever...
承运集装箱的人都应该知道
was supposed to pick that container up.
这也是为什么船停在港口
Which is why it stays on the dock.
起码我们要知道更多 关于那个港口货物是如何流通的信息
Bottom line is, we need to know more about cargo moving off that terminal.
怎样干勾当 干的时候如何隐蔽
How to do dirt. And how to hide when you're doing dirt.
我的"起码"不同
Bottom line for me is different.
我觉得起码 你们得扣留那艘船
Bottom line for me is, you guys should've held that ship.
考虑到犯罪现场 目击证人 考虑到它妈的整个案子
For your crime scene, for your witnesses, for the whole damn case.
长官 目击者...
Sir, the witnesses--
我才不管他们是不是操着基佬的中国话
I don't care if they were speaking Mandarin Chinese with a cocksucker's lisp.
他们得去审讯室一游 他们是案子的关键
They needed to see the inside of an interrogation room. They were the case.
我们在费城 没有管辖权
We were in Philadelphia, with no real jurisdiction...
处理外籍人员 也没有合理诉求
dealing with foreign nationals and no real probable cause.
我只能告诉你在我的位置上 我看到了什么
I can only tell you what it looks like from where I sit.
从这里 我看到我的俩个警探是饭桶
And from here, the view is two of my detectives fucking the dog.
13起谋杀案 如果我们算上浮尸 14起全部都需要侦破
Thirteen homicides, 14, if we connect the floater, and all of them red.
所以我能说什么呢?
So what can I tell you?
如果这案子不破 我们就得蛋疼地
If this case doesn't fall, we're all gonna be stepping on our dicks...
难以向公众交代
trying to explain what happened.
因此 你们看着办吧...
So, work it as you see fit...
但是丑话说前头
but understand...
到时候 我不得不丢给Burrell一两个替罪羊
if I have to throw Burrell a scapegoat or two...
我已经扔了一只了
I got one to throw.
我操
Fuck me.
你想和我们谈什么?
What did you want to talk to us about?
如果你们能像上次那样表现 我们还有别的需求
If you are able to do like you did, we have other things we can use.
比如?
Like what?
事实上 那次的照相机 已经被我们翻箱倒柜偷了个干净
Fact is, we shook things up down there snatching all them cameras.
如果还需要那样贵重的东西 得再等阵子才行
It comes to expensive shit like that, we got to lay back for a while.
我们不是要那样的东西
Stuff we need is not like that.
不是?
No?
丙酮 硫磺酸 高锰酸钾
Acetone, sulfuric acid, potassium permanganate.
化学品?
Chemicals?
就像涂料稀释剂
It's like paint thinner, shit like that.
你要这些干嘛? 去五金店买呗
What do you need with those? Just go get them at the hardware store.
不 我们需要很多
No. We need much.
好几吨  5吨或10吨
Metric tons. Five or ten tons.
查一下就知道了  这里有人制造这些东西
Check and you'll see, they make these things here.
东西都从这里运出去 集装箱一个接一个到你们码头
Send them from here. Tanks and tanks down at your docks.
这些东西可赚钱了
Good money for those.
多少?
How much?
能有多少化学品? 2吨? 4吨?
How much chemical? Two tons? Four?
- 8吨? - 我去查查看
- Eight? - I'll look into it.
嘿 Bubbles!
Yo, Bubbles!
McNulty
McNulty.
我的贱老弟
My meanest man.
上车
Get in the car.
最近忙什么呢 兄弟?
Where you been at, brother?
你们拿了啥?
What did you get?
随身听啊
Walkman.
你知道规矩的 Bubs 你要为这些玩意儿缴税
You know how it works, Bubs. You're going to pay taxes on this shit.
著名维权口号 要我纳税就给我代表权
"无代表 不纳税" 你没听说过吗?
Taxation without representation, you know?
我要的不多 只要Omar
I don't want much. I need Omar.
疯子Omar?
Wild Omar?
你要我们在城里转悠...
You want us to wander around town...
寻找一个持枪疯子?
Iooking for a crazy motherfucker with a shotgun?
他和我有交情 我找他没恶意
Him and me go way back, it's a friendly thing.
如果他是你的朋友 不用我们你也能找到那个混蛋
If he's a friend, you can find the motherfucker without us.
没问题 给我这玩意儿的收据 你们就可以走了
No problem. Show me the receipt for this shit, you're off the hook.
- 给 - 留着吧 算我的税
- Here. - Keep it, part of my tax.
你的税是Omar
Your tax is Omar.
我的期限是周五 Bubs
I need a line by Friday, Bubs.
操!
Fuck!
我的委托人会提供 劣质毒品来源的准确信息
My client will provide accurate information as to the source of the tainted narcotics.
他知道走私者将毒品 偷运进这所监狱的方法
He can identify the method by which contraband is smuggled into this institution,
和罪魁祸首
as well as the people responsible.
牢里的流言无足轻重
Cellblock talk is cheap.
他会给你结案所需的所有信息...
He'll give you what you need to make a case...
如果你们对此感兴趣的话
if that's what you're interested in.
你们的条件是?
Your terms?
Barksdale先生的第一次假释听证会是28月后
Mr. Barksdale is due for a first parole hearing at 28 months.
我们想把时间缩短到一年...
We'd like to trim that to a year...
并且希望得到贵监狱
and have your assurances of institutional support...
对进行监外就业和早释的保证
for work release and early parole.
7年缩减到1年?
One year on a seven-year bit?
我们提供的是全方位的配合
We are offering extraordinary cooperation in this matter.
Barksdale先生冒着风险
Mr. Barksdale's placing himself at risk...
提供涉案囚犯
by offering information implicating other prisoners...
和麻省监狱工作人员的信息
and staff at MCl.
我还要提一句Barksdale只是初犯
And I would only add that Mr. Barksdale's extant conviction is his first.
他没有任何前科
He has no priors whatsoever.
我记得本市一名警察 在Barksdale的生意中被枪击
It's my recollection that a city police got shot behind Mr. Barksdale's business.
不是的 警官
No, sir.
你不记得了吗?
You don't remember that?
我记得警官被枪击
I remember the officer got shot.
我记得为此感到不安 不仅仅是因为警官被枪击...
And I remember being upset about that, not only because the officer got shot...
还因为我知道这会使更多警察盯上我
but because I knew it meant there was gonna be more police on me.
我记得我想过"枪击一名警察简直傻透了"
I remember thinking, "Any time any fool do something like shoot a police...
"这对谁都没有好处"
"it's bad on everyone."
我知道你们明白
I know that you know that my name ain't nowhere...
我和你们的朋友受害完全无关
on what happened to your friend.
我想在现在的情况下 我们的要求很合理
I think what we're asking is reasonable under the circumstances.
毕竟 除非有人指出海洛因的来源
After all, until someone identifies the source of the tainted heroin...
否则明天或者后天
you could have another five overdoses tomorrow.
可能还有5人会吸食毒品过量
Or the day after.
考虑下吧
Consider the offer.
不过下一次我们谈话时 得有一名助理检察官在场
But the next time we talk an assistant attorney general has to be in the room.
晚餐吃金枪鱼吗?
Tuna surprise?
天啊 妈 今天我在两艘船上忙了一天了
Christ sakes, Ma, I climbed all over two ships today.
能不能吃点大餐啊?
How about a meal for that kind of day?
老爸呢?
Where's Pop?
他在酒吧研究马经呢
He's at the bar with the horses.
去告诉他吃晚饭了
Go tell him it's dinner.
我们赢了吗 老爸?
We winning, Pop?
Nicko
Nicko.
情况如何
You up today?
不错 不过今年"湾流"(估计是马名)真让我蛋疼
I was doing good, but this year Gulfstream is killing me.
悠着点 那可是我以后的遗产
Go easy. That's my inheritance.
25年来 我差不多还净赚7000美元
After 25 years, I'm still ahead almost $7,000.
Pimlico赌马场开门的时候 你该让我带你去
You ought to let me take you up to Pimlico when it opens.
真枪实弹试试你的系统
Try your system out for real.
太诱人了
Too tempting.
就一次
Just once.
我在西角看见了Cape Spruance号
Saw that the Cape Spruance is over at Point West.
嗯 我们今天卸了那艘船
Yeah, we offloaded her today.
你瞧 我们在四号口给她装过双壳
You know we double-hulled her down at number four.
大概是在船坞关门前两年吧
Maybe two years before the dry dock closed up.
她居然还能浮起来啊
She still floats?
她当然还能浮起来
Of course she still floats.
你怀念过从前吗 老爸?
You ever miss it, Pop?
怀念也没用啊
Wouldn't do no good.
晚饭吃什么?
What's for dinner?
金枪鱼大餐
Tuna surprise.
你对自己的人很有义气 至少我佩服这一点
You're loyal to your people. I respect that, at least.
别担心 警督
Don't worry, Lieutenant.
Burrell需要你带这个组  那我也不说二话
Burrell wants you on this detail, so I want you, too.
我需要你批准Freamon Greggs和Hauk
I need your approval for Freamon, Greggs, and Hauk.
他们都是刑侦科的人
They're all CID.
纠正一下
Correction.
你要的所有人都得经过我批准 这可能是Valchek发起的...
You need my approval for everyone. This may be Valchek's creation...
但是调查小组仍然隶属刑侦科
but the detail is investigative and comes under CID.
只要他们在我底下做事 就需要我的同意
If they work for me, they need my okay.
好消息是 我对你单子上的所有人都没意见
Good news is, I got no problem with anyone on your list.
除了McNulty
Except McNulty.
McNulty不行
No McNulty.
连长得像这混球的都不行
Nothing that even resembles the son of a bitch.
- 这么绝哈? - 他要么辞职 要么淹死
- That bad? - He quits or he drowns.
这是他离开那艘破船的唯一两个方法  我话撂这了
That's the only two things get him off the fucking boat, so help me God.
你知道这个专案组查什么吗 警督?
You even know what this detail's about, Lieutenant?
Valchek的眼中钉吧
Some kind of beef that Valchek has.
两个它妈的波兰人互相拆台
Two fucking Polacks pissing on each other's leg.
我听说了
I heard.
不过只要能让你离开那个地下室就行 是吗?
Anything to get you out of the basement, Lieutenant?
姑娘
Girl.
别! Kima 谁会当真?
No! Kima, who cares?
五分钟后我们就到了  而他们还是一群蠢货
We're gonna be there in five minutes and they'll still be dumbass frat boys.
你得想想 一名律师会怎么做?
You got to start thinking, what would a lawyer do?
一名律师会怎么说
What would a lawyer say?
Shakima Greggs阁下
Shakima Greggs, Esquire.
就是这样
That's what I'm talking about.
- 它妈的下来 蠢货 - 去你的 女士
- Get your ass down, fool. - Fuck you, lady.
我才不是女士
Ain't no lady.
- 贱人 再不开车就扣了 - 天啊 我们快走
- Bitch, drive it or lose it. - Oh, my God, let's get out of here.
"只有最好的品种才能表演得如此精湛 如此用心 如此顺从"
Only the finest breeds can perform this well, with this much heart and obedience.
"顺从造就冠军 不只是表演型犬...."
Obedience that brings out the champion not only in show dogs....
"看那虎虎生威的小狗"
Look at that tiger go.
"它是来自Glassport的冠军第三代后裔"
A third generation champion from Glassport.
"甚至它所在的宠物之家 都不知道它们有着冠军血统"
Even house pets that never knew they had the blood of champions in them.
"要表演到这种水平..."
To perform at this level...
"动物得毫不犹豫地服从命令"
an animal has to follow orders without question.
- "这不是本能" - 上楼吧
- It is not instinct. - Come on upstairs.
"所有的狗都有本能"
All dogs have instinct.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
这边没 大多数化学品都存在Fairfield中转站
Nothing's on this side. Most chemicals are over at the Fairfield terminals.
那有我们认识的吗?
Who do we know at Fairfield?
Ott的小舅子在那里工作
Ott's brother-in-law works there.
你可以试试联系他
You might try and touch him.
不过他们要这些干嘛呢?
What do they want with those for, anyway?
问倒我了
Beats the fuck out of me.
- 天啊 抱歉 - 操 哥们 妈的
- Jesus, I'm sorry. - Fuck, man, shit.
我没看见你穿着漂亮的皮大衣在那儿
I didn't see you standing there in all that sweet leather.
- 你它妈的什么毛病啊? - 我想是笨拙吧
- What the fuck is wrong with you? - Clumsy, I guess.
你可以去偷一大箱婴儿纸巾...
You can just go out and steal a whole can full of baby wipes...
把自己擦干净
and just clean yourself up.
你这个鸟人
You fucking goof.
混蛋
Dick.
该死 队长 我发过誓
Shit, Lieutenant, I promised.
你以为我老婆听说这事儿会欢呼万岁吗
Think my woman's gonna give a great big cheer when she hears about it?
我被关在门外
I was out the damn door.
你不懂Cheryl
You don't know Cheryl.
你不懂Marla
You don't know Marla.
如果你愿意...
If you want...
我可以让你干内勤 就像我们去年让Prez干的那样
I could use you inside, like we did Prez last year.
类似听到冲锋号 就要上战场
听到音乐 我就要起舞
If I hear the music, I'm gonna dance.
只要你通知我老婆 我就去通知你的
I'll tell your wife, if you tell mine.
放进车里 但不要太显眼
In the car, but not out in the open.
嘿 Rock
Yo, Rock.
要不露痕迹
Be subtle with it, man.
懂这意思吧
You know what subtle means?
就是随意点
Laid back and shit.
音色不错吧 老爹?
Good tunes, Pop?
嗯
Yeah.
谢谢这耳麦
Thanks for the phones.
我不知道 Bubs 我是说
I don't know, Bubs. I mean...
如果常在河边走
if you go rolling over rocks...
哪能不湿鞋呢?
then you're gonna get bit by a snake, right?
得缴税啊 Johnny
Got to pay that tax, Johnny.
欠警察的总得还
You got to give a working police his due.
- 也就是说Bee为Lamar干活? - 所有人都为Lamar干活
- So, Bee's working for Lamar? - All of them work for Lamar.
那一块他是老大
He got that whole corner to hisself.
你说藏毒点是街对面平房区?
You saying the stash is across the street in the low-rises?
在第二个院子里
In the second court.
窗户被钉死的地方
They got it up in this one place that got the boarded-up windows.
从头上数有几扇门?
How many doors down from the end?
三扇
Three.
嘿 老爹
Yo, Pops.
有谁有那个拿着猎枪 打家劫舍的疯子的消息?
Anyone got a line on that wild boy who likes to pop the shotty?
- Omar? - 嗯 我要找Omar
- Omar? - Yeah, I need Omar.
你找Omar干什么?
What do you want with Omar?
就想和他说句话
Just want a word with him.
就说句话
Just a word.
你想找Omar...
You want to get with Omar...
就带着一大袋货站在街角
you need to stand out on one of them corners with a big-ass package.
这样你就很快就能和他说上话了
You be talking to that nigger soon enough.
爽了吗?
You feel anything?
走吧
Let's go.
来吧
Come on.
按照协议 合作的条件是州假释官同意...
As agreed, the price of cooperation is an agreement by the state parole officials...
让Barksdale先生的第一次 假释听证会提前12个月
to move Mr. Barksdale's first parole hearing forward by 12 months...
并且在档案中记他一功
and to credit him in the file with cooperation in this matter.
就靠一个骗子的话还不能结案
You can't make a case on just some con's say so.
我们要拿赃
We need the dope on the table.
这是当然
Of course you do.
如果 在今天结束前 你下令搜查
If, before the end of business today, you effect a search...
狱警Tilghman的车子 物品柜以及本人
of Correctional Officer Tilghman's vehicle, locker, and person...
我们相信就会发现足够的证据
we are confident sufficient evidence will be recovered.
"我们相信"?
"We are confident"?
监狱总局觉得 如果能了解此案
As far as D.O.C. is concerned, this is a fair deal...
这个交易很公平
if it takes the overdoses off our plate.
可如果我们空手而回
But if we come up empty on this....
不会的
You won't.
这事板上钉钉
Five will get you ten...
这混蛋就是掺毒的幕后主使
that's the motherfucker that spiked the packages.
你有证据吗?
You have proof of this?
那就做我们能做的 把案子结了
Then we make the case that's there for us to make.
邮戳:新奥尔良 2003.3.1
额滴神啊 新奥尔良
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph. New Orleans.
警督
Lieutenant.
欢迎来到东南区
Welcome to the southeast.
警长 我知道你点名要我来
Major, I understand you asked for me.
我女婿一个劲地说你好
My son-in-law can't say enough in your favor.
当然 你去年也帮了他一把 不是吗
And, of course, you did him a good turn last year, right?
你和我说说这个目标人物吧
You want to tell me about this target?
Frank Sobotka
Frank Sobotka.
港口工会的人
A union man down at the port.
这操蛋的富得流油
The motherfucker's showing a lot of money.
我敢说和毒品有关
My gut says a drug connection.
我还可以肯定地告诉你 他的人...
I can also tell you for a fact that his people...
会偷任何可以搬动的东西
will up and steal anything that isn't nailed down.
- 你去办公室驻地看过了吗? - 还没有
- You seen the off-site? - Not yet.
我让我的人在这里碰头
I told my people to meet up here, at the district.
那地方不错 来吧 我带你看看
Pretty good digs. Come on, I'll show you.
这是一位年轻女人写给她母亲的...
It's from a young woman to her mother...
或者至少写给一个年长的女人
or at least an older woman.
她提到什么名字吗?
She mention any names?
这里有一个Anya
There is an Anya here.
从她的写作方式看 我猜是个孩子
And from the way she writes, I'm guessing it is a child.
快好了 神父 抱歉请等一下
It's almost ready, Father. Excuse me.
她写给谁呢?
So who's she writing to?
没有写名字
There is no name.
这封信是写给所有家人的
The letter is for the whole family.
可是...
But...
她署名"Nadya" 她的名字是Nadya
she signs, "Nadya." Her name is Nadya.
Nadya
Nadya.
她有麻烦了?
Is she in trouble?
她死了
She's dead.
信里有说这些人住哪儿吗?
Anything in the letter to indicate as to where these people live?
如果你有信封 我可以....
If you had an envelope, I could....
她唯一具体提到的是一所教堂...
The only thing specific she mentions, is a church...
圣Volodymyr或者是圣Vladimir 和一位牧师
St. Volodymyr, or St. Vladimir, and a priest.
- Vasyl神父 信上说 - 没有名字或者地址或者....
- Father Vasyl, it says. - There's no names or places or....
大洋彼岸 Vasyl神父 这个名字很常见
Across the water, Father Vasyl is a common name...
而且还有很多圣Volodymyrs教堂
and there are many St. Volodymyrs.
不过把信留下吧 我试试
But leave the letter. I will try.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我只是说 如果活不多 你可以干点别的啊
I'm saying, if there isn't enough work, then you could do something else, that's all.
活够多了
There's enough work.
事实上 我刚收到一个月前的欠款
Fact is, I came into some back pay I was owed from about a month ago.
在旅行基金里也有几千元
A couple thousand from the vacation fund.
停下吧 Ash
Stop, Ash.
我在想...
I was thinking...
或许是时候我们买房子了
maybe this'll be the time for us to get a place.
你付得起吗?
You could cover that?
或许我们不用租房
And maybe we don't rent.
或许我们试着在小区里买栋房子
Maybe we try and buy something in the neighborhood.
不用很大 只要...
Nothing too big, just....
我听说Treesey婶婶 在Covington的旧房子翻修得不错
I heard Aunt Treesey's old place up in Covington has been fixed up real nice.
镶了木地板之类的
Like with wood floors and all.
Ash 那边那艘是什么船?
Ash, what's that ship right there?
放缆船(从事海底电缆敷设)
Cable ship.
旁边那艘灰色的呢?
And what's the gray one next to it?
军用补给船
Military Sealift.
聪明囡
Attagirl.
你冷吗?
You cold?
Dwight?
咋了?
What's up?
我们得搜你的车 抱歉
We're gonna have to search your vehicle. Sorry.
- 搜车? 搞什么啊? - 打开车门
- Search? What the fuck? - Open it,
否则我撬开车门 可能就会弄坏你的车
or I'm gonna shim the lock, maybe damage your ride.
你没有权力这么对我
You got no call to be doing me like this.
- 既没权力也没有搜查令 - 你的车停在监狱总局的辖地
- No call and no damn warrant. - You drive onto a D.O.C. facility...
你理应知晓车也是搜查目标(如同入狱时要搜身)
you acknowledge the vehicle's subject to search.
钥匙呢 Dwight?
Where's the key, Dwight?
他随时可能吃完午饭回来 Zig
He's gonna be back from lunch any minute, Zig.
你听见了吗?
You hear me?
他看你摆弄那东西 他会把你拆了
He sees you on that thing he's gonna break you down
一块一块地卖了
and sell you for parts.
在这里
Here it be.
是你们栽赃的!
You all planted that shit.
你们它妈的心知肚明
You fucking know you did.
- 口哨是怎么回事? - 是因为我们
- What's with the whistle squad? - It's for us.
我们一下车 就被盯上了
They marked us the moment we stepped out of the car.
就是他
That's him.
他是"马面"?
That's Horseface?
- 他怎么有这个名字? - 你还要特写镜头吗?
- How did he get the name? - You need a close-up?
Thomas Pakusa
Thomas Pakusa.
嗯
yeah?
我们有事要和你谈谈
We need to talk to you about something.
谈什么?
What?
当Atlantic Light号靠岸时 你是检查员吧 对吧?
You were working the Atlantic Light when it docked, right?
你说什么就是什么
If you say so.
你记得那天卸下来的集装箱吗?
You remember that container that came off that day?
里面都是死去的女孩子
With all the dead girls.
不记得
No.
你不记得她们都死在一个集装箱里?
You don't remember all them dead girls in a can?
得了吧 马面
Come on, Horse.
我记得你在堆货区发现她们
I remember when you found them all in the stacks.
我不记得她们是从Atlantic Light号下来的
I don't remember they came off the Atlantic Light.
去警局一趟 把事情弄清楚
Let's take a ride downtown, clear this mess up.
没门
No.
它妈的上车
Get the fuck in the car.
- 你要拷我吗? - 该死的给我上车
- Am I locked up? - Get in the damn car.
你要我上车 你得把我拷起来
You want me in that car, you need to lock me up.
如果是那样的话 我要找我的工会管事...
If that's the way it'll be, I wanna talk to my shop steward...
他可以找名工会律师和我一起出去
and he can have an IBS lawyer go with me.
爸 你...
Dad, what--
天啊 老爸 干嘛打我?
Jesus, Pop, what's that for?
说茄子
Say cheese.
你再耍滑头 Zig 小心我收了你的卡
You pull another stunt like that, Zig, I'll have your damn card.
我才不管你妈是谁呢
I don't care who your mother is.
它妈的给我滚!
Get the fuck out of here!
真是个聪明的胖子 对吧?
Kind of smart for a fat man, isn't he?
好吧
All right.
该死的 Ziggy 你这个变态的杂种
Goddamn it, Ziggy, you sick fuck.
让你的老二滚出我的电脑!
Get your dick out of my computer!
第一次调来的警察呢?
Where are the detectives who were first assigned?
死了
Dead.
对我来说是的
To me, anyway.
我一刻不停地把他们打发回Burrell那儿了
I shipped them humps back to Burrell as fast as I could.
什么事耽搁了这么久?
What kept you?
这个警局就是这样美好
That's the beautiful thing about this department.
连脑死的人都能站起来
Every brain-dead somehow manages to land on his feet.
- 过得好吗 Prez? - 你过得怎样?
- How's it hanging, Prez? - How're you doing?
挺好的
I'm all right.
Lester呢?
Where's Lester?
我们还有他 对吧?
We got him, too, right?
他今天上街 办凶杀组的案子...
He was out on the street today with Homicide...
Rawls答应明天告诉他这个"噩耗"
but Rawls promised to give him the bad news tomorrow.
不过没有McNulty
Not McNulty though.
他们把McNulty恨到骨子里去了 不过我也不怪他们
McNulty they really hate, not that I blame them.
当然 办案期间 Roland也是你的人
You, of course, have Roland for the duration.
任何东南区里你需要的人都没问题
Anyone else from the southeastern you need, you got.
那就不打扰了
I'll leave you to it, then.
队长
Lieutenant
Carver现在在东南区了 我想他去二支队了吧
Carver's in the southeast, now. I think he's got Sector Two.
要是Carver也插一脚就更棒了 是吧?
It'd be great to have Carver on this, right?
参与什么?
On what?
我们都不知道我们在查什么
We don't even know what the hell we're supposed to be chasing here.
无意冒犯你的老丈人 可真的是无凭无据
No offense to your father-in-law, but it's real thin.
我们已经来了 是吧? 不管发生什么 我们跟进这个案子几个星期
We're here, right? Whatever happens, we run with the program for a few weeks.
可能查到港口一两件贩毒案
Maybe make a drug case or two down by the port.
给物证处看看我们的厉害
Beats the hell out of E.C.U. anyway.
他和这个女人有了个女儿 她先天哑巴
Him and this lady have this daughter. The daughter's born a mute.
妻子很不喜欢 就出走了
The wife doesn't like that at all, so she breaks out.
这个人就自己抚养女儿 她来了月事...
So this guy's raising his daughter, she has her period...
吓坏了 去找他 他以为她被强奸了...
freaks out, goes to him, he thinks she was raped--
发横财了
Jackpot.
那金属能卖10美元呢
That's about $10 worth of bulk metal right there.
我们只要把它拖到收破烂的院子就行
We just have to haul it down to the scrap yard and we're good.
我们它妈的会把背给折掉的
We'll break our fucking backs on this thing.
虚心点 好吗 我在教你呢
Keep your eye to the ground, okay? I'm schooling you.
成么?
Okay?
好极了 这东西
This is good, right here.
值10美元呢
This is $10 right here.
偷鸡摸狗的Bubs(也有告密之意)
Snitching Bubs.
你找我?
You be asking for me?
耳麦真赞 我可以在健身房用 谢了
These headphones are great. I'm gonna use them at the gym. Thanks.
- 你听到孩子们的声音了? - 没有 挺安静的
- You hear the boys? - No, it's quiet up there.
有些太安静了
A little too quiet.
这说明他们可能在打游戏
That means they're probably playing video games.
或者在玩火柴
Or with a book of matches.
那么 你让律师看过文件了吗
So, did you have a lawyer look at the papers yet?
看过了
I did.
然后呢?
And?
他说我不该签
He says I shouldn't sign it.
说我给得太多了
Says I'm giving away too much.
如果我们上法庭
I would never, under any circumstances...
我绝不用付笔那么贵的赡养费...
pay that kind of support and alimony if we went to court.
他这么说?
That's what he says?
签过 公证过
Signed and notarized.
我不想计较这钱
I don't wanna argue about the money.
我想复和
I wanna get back together.
进
Yeah.
嘿 String 我干得不露痕迹
Yo, String, I was subtle with that.
...将对三名囚犯提出毒品分销罪的起诉
...has led to drug distribution charges against three inmates...
其中一名囚犯
one who was, himself, incapacitated...
因吸食被污染的毒品而瘫痪  同时起诉的还有一名
by the tainted narcotics and the correctional officer...
有10年资历的狱警
a 10-year veteran.
依照监狱长
I've been instructed by the Corrections Commissioner...
和公共安全秘书长的指示
and the State Public Safety Secretary...
宣布这位警官...
to announce that the maximum penalties...
将受到最严厉的处罚....
will be sought against this officer....
我有期中考试呢 得学习了
I got a midterm. I got to study.
这就是他们聚点?
So this is their joint?
有什么计划?
What's the plan?
是时候让他们知道我们是不会罢休的
Time to make it clear to these people that we're not gonna go away.
你不会是想播乡村乐吧?
You ain't gonna play that country shit, right?
我可不好这口
I hate that country shit.
就算是Ray Charles(著名灵魂乐手)唱的也不行
Not even Ray Charles can save that mess for me.
不 先生
No, sir.
上世纪50年代 橄榄球大联盟著名防守前锋
"大老爹"Lipscomb是右内边锋
Big Daddy Lipscomb was right tackle.
你昏头了吧 Jessy
Your brain's gone to shit, Jessy.
是左内边锋
Left tackle.
你混账事干多了 左右都不分
You was too busy pissing in your drawers to learn left from right.
著名橄榄球餐厅 墙上有很多珍贵照片
去Schula's Steakhouse学学吧
Take your ass down to Schula's Steakhouse and get an education.
亲爱的
Darling.
啥事?
What's the deal?
就是来喝两杯 然后走人
Just dropping in for one or two and then we take ourselves out of here.
你呢?
How about you?
这杯喝完我就走
I'm leaving after this one.
你们是港口警察吗? 我不认识你们
You guys Port Police? I don't recognize either one of you.
市局凶杀科
City Homicide.
凶杀科?
Homicide?
- 谁被杀了? - 那些集装箱里的女尸
- Who got killed? - Those dead girls in the can.
那是个意外
That was an accident.
它妈的是个意外
That was a fucking accident.
至少我是这么听说的
That's what I heard, anyway.
借过
Excuse me.